{

  "Data":[{"Question":"第一題，1+3=幾多","Answer":[{"0":"0","1":"0","4":"10","3":"0"}]},
          {"Question":"第二題，3+5=幾多","Answer":[{"4":"0","8":"10","2":"0","3":"0"}]},
          {"Question":"第三題，2+4=幾多","Answer":[{"3":"0","6":"10","11":"0","2":"0"}]},
          {"Question":"第四題，4+4=幾多","Answer":[{"8":"10","9":"0","2":"0","7":"0"}]},
          {"Question":"第五題，3+5=幾多","Answer":[{"4":"0","8":"10","2":"0","3":"0"}]},
          {"Question":"第六題，7—3=幾多","Answer":[{"4":"10","1":"0","7":"0","3":"0"}]},
          {"Question":"第七題，9—6=幾多","Answer":[{"9":"0","1":"0","5":"0","3":"10"}]},
          {"Question":"第八題，11—2=幾多","Answer":[{"7":"0","8":"0","9":"10","6":"0"}]},
          {"Question":"第九題，8—5=幾多","Answer":[{"4":"0","2":"0","1":"0","3":"10"}]},
          {"Question":"第十題，6—6=幾多","Answer":[{"0":"10","1":"00","2":"0","3":"0"}]}
         
         ]}
